(Leonard:)You need to watch Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
The perfect show for the two of us.
(Leonard:)It's got action and jokes and hot vampires
and romance. I cannot oversell this.
(Leonard:)What do you say?
It's 6:30 in the morning.
(Leonard:)I thought you grew up on a farm.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, Syfy Network,
this is your vice president of programing.
(Sheldon(on phone):)We have made a horrible mistake
regarding Alphas.
(Sheldon(on phone):)We need to uncancel it immediately.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Put me through
to the people who handle that.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Tell them it's me.
I don't wanna answer a lot of questions...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...about if I really am who I say I am.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I just... I want this done.
No, I'm not the person who just called.
(Sheldon(on phone):)That man was clearly a cowboy...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...concerned about y'all
canceling his favorite show.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Why do they keep hanging up on me?
(Amy:)I'm sorry you're upset.